funmunch.com 2017-12-15

# Privacy Policy - Funmunch.com

Funmunch.com is firmly committed to the privacy of our users' personal information. Our staff, contractors and others who help us operate our web site follow this policy on privacy and fair information practices for online activities of FunMunch.com. We outline here the information-collection procedure and usage practices for our website, www.funmunch.com. By using this website, you agree to accept this Privacy Policy and are aware that our policy may change over time as discussed below.

To browse the pages at Funmunch.com you do not require to give up any personal information. Only when you register as a member, we collect Personal Information including your email address, first name, last name, and birthday, or any information that is voluntarily provided by you while creating your Profile. All data that we collect from you is stored on one or more secure database servers that cannot be accessed from outside our corporate network.

Through our sites, access to personal information is completely controlled by user-defined e-mail addresses and passwords. Within our company, access to data is secured through a private user ID and password known only to personnel who have a need to know such information to perform their essential job functions. We will continue to use reasonable efforts to ensure the protection of your Personal Information.

**Personal Details**  
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

Funmunch.com takes necessary precautions to safeguard the privacy of data you input. The data that we collect from you like username, e-mail address, and password are used to uniquely identify you as a user on Funmunch. We may use or display your username for the purposes of rankings, competitions or sweepstakes, chat identification, and/or game high scores.  
Your contact details can also be used to notify you about new features, enhancements, resolution of site problems, your customer support questions and issues, and inform you of upgrade opportunities, sweepstakes, contests, prizes, and/or special events. However, we never disclose your e-mail address on our site or in any other form. 

**Cookies**  
~~~~~~~

Funmunch.com uses or may use cookies to improve the use of our websites. A "cookie" is a small file that websites often store on a user's computer. Storage of cookies on your system provides an easy and convenient method for us to personalize your experience on our websites. For example, cookies allow us to remember your screen name, tell us that you have visited our website before, and may contain information that will make your next visit to our website more enjoyable. However, we do not use cookies to store personal information such as your name. In addition, Funmunch does not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. You can always disable cookies or set your browser to alert you when cookies are being sent to your computer. 

**IP Addresses**  
~~~~~~~~~~~~~

Funmunch.com may also collect your IP address for safety and security purposes. An IP address is a numeric address that is assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet. In the event of abuse, however, we may block certain IP addresses or may disclose them to the concerned authorities.

Funmunch may maintain log files which contain IP addresses. We do not link IP addresses to personal information. In general, we only use log files to monitor traffic on our Websites and to troubleshoot technical problems.

 **Third Party Advertising**  
~~~~~~~~~~~~~

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, **[click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.

  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.

  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the **[Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)**.

**Third Party Sites & Links**  
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

To provide relevant information not found on our Web site, Funmunch may provide links from our Web sites to third party Web sites and we encourage our users to read third party sites' privacy policies before submitting personal information. Funmunch.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of the content of third party sites. Funmunch.com hereby disclaims any representations or warranties expressed on any site other than its own site.

 **Questions or Suggestions**   
~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~

To review, modify or remove the information you have provided to us, or to contact us with any questions or complaints, please e-mail us at [ myfunmunch@gmail.com](mailto:myfunmunch@gmail.com)

By using this site, you signify your acceptance to the funmunch.com Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy may be reviewed from time to time. We will thereby request you to review this Privacy Policy over the period of time to be informed of how funmunch.com protects your information.

 **Last Updated - 1st December, 2009**
